Guide to the Doris Duke Oral History Collection, 1998-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Records, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Oral History Project, Audio cassettes transfer project pilot program, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Safe Sound information, including statement of work, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Oral History Project, Audio cassettes transfer, 2008 (Box 14)